The schedule’s tight on the cluster tonight
So I parallelized my code
All those threads and continuations
My head’s going to explode
And all that boilerplate
That FactoryBuilderAdapterDelegateImpl
Seems unjustified
Give me something simple
Don’t write in Scheme
Don’t write in C
No more pointers
that I forgot to free()
Java’s verbose
Python’s too slow
It’s time you know
Write in Go!
No inheritance anymore
There’s no do or while,
just for
I don’t care what your linters say
I’ve got tools for that
The code never bothered me anyway
It’s funny how some features
Make every change seem small
And the errors that once slowed me
Don’t get me down at all
It’s time to see what Go can do
’Cause it seems too good to be true
No long compile times for me.
I’m free!
Write in Go!
Kiss your pointer math goodbye
Time to give GC a try
I don’t care if my structures stay
On the heap or stack
My program spawns its goroutines
without a sound
Control is spiraling through
buffered channels all around
I don’t remember why I ever once subclassed
I’m never going back
My tests all build and pass
Write in Go!
You won’t use Eclipse anymore
Who cares what Boost is for?
I don’t care what the tech leads say
I’ll rewrite it all!
Writing code never bothered me, anyway.